Bonus Short Stories

Because I’m Drowsy

One sunny morning, before Rio had taken Celia to deliver the letter to Count Claire’s residence...

Rio, Aishia, and Celia were sleeping side by side in the giant bed of the stone house as per usual. However —

“Mm. Mrgh...”

Celia suddenly woke up. Her former dedication to her research meant that her sleep pattern was disrupted often, which made her a light sleeper that was used to waking up after a short amount of sleep. Celia sat up slowly, looking around the room with a drowsy look. Rio was sleeping beside her, and Aishia was sleeping beside him. Aishia was clinging to Rio’s arm, breathing peacefully in her deep sleep.

“Mmm...”

Aishia suddenly stirred. Then, something squished against Rio’s arm.

“...”

Celia watched the scene while still half asleep. After a moment, she slowly looked down at her own chest. Another moment later, she looked back at Aishia’s chest.

Squeeze, squeeze. Squish, squish.

It wasn’t enough. It was admittedly soft to touch, but there was still something squishy missing.

“Hmph...”

Celia was still half asleep, but she pouted in frustration. She was used to being sleep deprived, but both her mind and body weren’t rested enough, so she snuggled into the blankets once more. Spurred on by Aishia, she boldly pressed herself close to Rio... As a result, Rio was sandwiched between Aishia and Celia.

“...”

When something soft from Celia’s side squished against his arm, Rio faintly stiffened. But the drowsy Celia paid no attention to that and continued to cling to Rio innocently. It was something she would never do on a regular day.

“...”

Aishia clung closer to Rio, as though competing with Celia.

“......”

Rio was completely frozen with his eyes closed. With Celia in a sleepy daze and Aishia unconsciously clinging to him, he had nowhere to go. He was perfectly restrained. In the end, Rio remained frozen between the two clinging girls for nearly an hour.

D-Did you see?

While Rio was interfering with Celia’s wedding ceremony in Strahl, shortly after Miharu and the others were taken to the spirit village...

Is it morning? Miharu suddenly woke up. She had stayed up late studying, so she was rather tired. However, she suppressed her sleepiness and rose from bed to fulfill her breakfast duties.

What should I make today? Miharu pondered drowsily as she took off her sleeping gown. Once she was down to her underwear, she picked out a change of clothes from the drawer and placed it on her bed. After taking off the bra she wore while sleeping to change into her everyday bra, she put on her clothes with familiar movements.

Okay, I’m ready! ...Huh? What’s that nice smell?

Miharu sniffed, nose twitching at the faint scent of cooking.

Is that Haruto or Orphia? I should help too.

Miharu hurried to leave the room, but someone knocked on the door first. Caught off guard, Miharu responded reflexively. “Ah, yes?”

“Miharu, I came to call you for breakfast.” Rio was on the other side.

“...Huh? Ah, did I sleep in? I’m sorry!” Miharu opened the door in a panic, bowing her head at Rio.

“It’s fine. I sleep in sometimes too. Don’t worry about it...” Rio replied with a faint smile. When he spotted the bra left on the bed behind Miharu, he averted his eyes awkwardly.

“Haruto?” Miharu tilted her head curiously.

“Nothing, don’t worry about it. I’ll be waiting, then.” With that, Rio departed with haste.

“Yes? I’ll be right there too.” Miharu was curious as to why Rio averted his gaze and turned back. Then —

“?!”

She spotted her own discarded bra. It was in full view from the door, folded neatly on top of her nightgown. She was the one who had put it there, after all.

D-Did he see it? Miharu’s face reddened by the minute. Afterward, while they were eating breakfast, Rio and Miharu averted their eyes from each other in embarrassment the entire time.

Elemental☆Element, Teacher?

In the middle of spring in Japan, Amakawa Haruto and Ayase Miharu were childhood friends that just started their second year of high school this spring.

It was morning, just before homeroom. Today was the day of the opening ceremony, and everyone was excited about the class shuffle, leaving the classrooms bustling with lively conversation. Among them were Haruto and Miharu.

“Looks like we’re in the same class this year, Haru-kun,” Miharu said happily as she took the seat next to Haruto.

“So it seems,” Haruto replied to Miharu awkwardly.

The two were in different classes during their first year, but they would be in the same class from today onwards. And on top of that, they were seat neighbors.

Amakawa Haruto and Ayase Miharu. In their high school, seat numbers were assigned by gender in order of family name, so it was only natural for the two of them to be given the same seat number. As a result, it was inevitable for the two of them to be seated beside each other. Even if the seat numbers had been decided by birthdate, the two were both born in spring and would have been given the same seat numbers anyway.

They’d been separated for a long time, but after reuniting a year ago, they couldn’t help but feel like fate was working for them.

“Let’s get along this year, Haru-kun,” Miharu said to Haruto with wholehearted happiness in her tone.

“Agreed,” Haruto replied, still a little awkward.

However, the two were a very attractive pair that stood out within the class.

“Ah, I wonder if those two are dating. I can’t believe this is happening after I’m finally placed in the same class as Ayase...”

The male students all sighed together. Meanwhile —

“Aww, I’m finally in the same class as Amakawa, but I’m no match for Ayase. I can’t believe this...”

The female students all sighed, too. However —

“Hey hey, it’s too early to be disappointed, guys. Didn’t you see who our teacher is? It’s Professor Celia,” one of the male students said to the others.

“Seriously?!” The boys all regained their vigor immediately.

Celia Claire was the lecturer that transferred to their high school from overseas last year. Her adorable looks that made her appear younger than everyone made her highly popular among both boys and girls. As they gossiped about Celia, the door to the classroom opened.

“Ooh...!” the male students all cheered at once.

It was Celia who had entered. However, as it was still early in the morning, she seemed rather lethargic. But despite that, the male students paid no attention to Celia’s exhaustion, caught in their own excitement.

“We still have Professor Celia!”

“What are you all talking about?” Celia replied tiredly to the boys as she stood at the teacher’s desk. “Oh well. I’m going to introduce you to someone, though she’ll be officially introduced later at the entrance ceremony. Come in, Aishia.”

With a heavy sigh, she called down the hallway. A peach-haired girl appeared in the open doorway.

“...” The students were all captivated by the beauty of the girl and gulped in shock.

Celia grimaced at the reaction of the students. “Aishia, introduce yourself,” she urged.

“I’m Aishia,” Aishia said, offering only her name.

“That isn’t an introduction...” Celia placed a hand against her face in clear exhaustion. But Aishia paid no heed to her, glancing around the classroom instead. Her gaze stopped on Haruto.

“...There you are,” Aishia muttered, swiftly approaching Haruto.

“Huh?” Haruto looked taken aback in confusion.

“Aishia Amakawa. I’ll be with Haruto from today onwards. Wait for me after class; we’ll go home together.” Aishia suddenly said, shocking everyone in the room.

“Wha?!” Seated beside Haruto, Miharu was also speechless.

“Eeeeh?!”

The yells of the students echoed through the school.

To be continued... maybe?

I tried to dance!

At the village where the spirit folk live...

Just before supper, Latifa had shut herself alone in her room, sitting on a chair. Her chin was resting on her left arm as she held a pen in her right hand, hemming and hawing in the direction of her desk.

What kind of uniform would be cute, I wonder?

She was pondering over the design of her own uniform. She had decided to make a uniform after seeing Miharu and Aki’s Japanese school uniforms earlier today. Having died as a primary school student, Latifa — no, Suzune — admired the uniforms middle school and high school students wore. Unable to suppress her impatience, she took out her writing tools in an attempt to come up with her own design, but...

What kind of uniform would Onii-chan like?

She was having trouble coming up with anything specific. Designing wasn’t an easy task for an amateur to begin with.

“Mmrgh...” Latifa groaned.

While Miharu and Orphia would be the ones making the uniform, she couldn’t just leave everything to them if she wanted to surprise Rio. She at least wanted to come up with her own ideas.

What would Onii-chan say if he saw me in a uniform? Would he call me cute?

Latifa giggled with a smile. “Cute.” If she could hear that one word from Rio, she would ecstatic. Simply imagining it was enough to make her happy.

Hmm, but just wearing a uniform seems a little boring... no? What if I danced or something as well? Latifa suddenly thought to herself, tilting her head.

“...I wonder what kind of dance would be good?”

She stood up and imagined herself wearing a uniform. Her room had plenty of empty space, so she stood in the middle of an open area.

“Like this, perhaps?” Latifa shyly took a step. Eventually, she realized she needed to move her hands too and added to the choreography. She started having more and more fun as time passed.

“One, two. One, two.” Latifa danced in a fairly convincing way, taking light steps and moving her limbs rhythmically.

“Hmm hm hmm...” She started humming along. She was excited about it, so the choreography ideas came to her one after another too.

Should I think of some lyrics too? Latifa wondered, but lyrics didn’t come to her so easily. She took several moments to wonder what would be good. Perhaps it would be best to express her feelings honestly. Which meant —

“‘I love you, Onii-chan’?”

That was it. Before she knew it, her mouth was moving naturally. Then, at the most climactic moment, she spun around and made her final pose. Since she was a werefox, she emphasized her fox side with rhythmic fox-like hops. Latifa’s gaze suddenly moved to the door. Come to think of it, she had left it wide open. In the doorway stood a frozen Miharu.

“Wait, Miharu?!” Latifa’s body shook with a flinch.

“Ah, s-sorry. I heard you humming and your door was open so I tried calling out to you a few times, but there was no reply...” Miharu apologized in a fluster.

“W-Were you watching?” Latifa asked with a bright red face.

“U-Umm. Just the final part,” Miharu hesitantly confirmed.

“Mwuuuh!”

Latifa hid her face behind her hands and crouched down on the spot. She was so embarrassed, her face felt like it was on fire.

“I-I’m sorry.” Miharu ran over to Latifa in a panic and held up her body.

“...It’s not your fault, Miharu. I was the one who left my door open. Uugh, but I’m still so embarrassed!” Latifa groaned in agony. She was so absorbed in her thoughts about Rio that she hadn’t noticed anything around her at all. She had some serious reflecting to do...

“I-It was really cute, though,” Miharu offered honestly, trying to cheer Latifa up.

“...T-Thanks. By the way, what did you need, Miharu?” Latifa’s fox ears twitched as she asked shyly.

“Oh. I came to call you, since the food will be ready soon...”

“...Got it. This is a secret between the two of us, okay, Miharu?”

“Yup, I know.” Miharu nodded with a faintly strained smile. She wasn’t a big gossiper to begin with.

“...If you tell anyone, I’ll have you dance with me in front of Onii-chan. Got it?” Latifa pouted her lips in a sulk.

“E-Eeeh?! M-Me too?! No way!” Miharu shook her head reflexively.

“You’ll be fine if you don’t say anything.”

“I-I see. Right. That makes sense. Got it. Yup, okay.” Miharu nodded to convince herself.

“...It’s a promise, then. Let’s go.”

Latifa grinned gently and walked out of the room. Miharu giggled before bringing up the rear.

Chapter 4: Apology

Later that night, in an office inside Liselotte’s estate in Amande...

“...And that is what happened. The employee inside the room and staff outside the room were all present for the whole ordeal and their testimonies match each other, so it is safe to presume these as the facts,” Aria reported to Liselotte and Duke Huguenot in a flat voice. She had just finished explaining the trouble Stewart and Alphonse had caused.

The guest chairs in the room were occupied by Liselotte and Duke Huguenot, who each had a pained expression on their faces. An uncomfortable air flowed throughout the room.

“...I am truly sorry for this,” Duke Huguenot said after a pause. He was seated across from Liselotte; he bowed his head deeply at her.

“No... Well, let’s see... For now, I’ll accept your apology,” Liselotte said, accepting Duke Huguenot’s apology in a stuttering tone; she had no choice since something had in fact happened, and there were other things to prioritize before sinking time into finding out who was responsible right now.

“Those fools...” Duke Huguenot muttered under his breath in a terrifyingly cold voice.

“And what about Sir Haruto?” Liselotte sighed quietly before turning to address Aria.

“As it is already late at night and Haruto was the obvious victim in this case, on top of being our valued guest, I have asked him to rest at the inn. I did offer him an apology on the scene in a rush, but I informed him that you would be apologizing to him directly tomorrow, master,” Aria replied respectfully. She had been the one to gather all the details at the inn.

Stewart and Alphonse’s fuss had been overheard by not only the staff, but some of the customers as well, so there was no way for them to excuse themselves.

Furthermore, the employee inside the room had given a testimony as a third party, and the staff on standby outside the room had also been watching the situation quietly, all confirming that none of the fault fell on Rio. On top of that, the girls who had gone there with Stewart and Alphonse testified that the two boys were the ones at fault once they had been removed from the room. They felt no reason to go out of their way to protect the two, especially once the person in charge of overseeing their city appeared in the flesh.

At that point, Rio was courteously returned to his room while Stewart and Alphonse were restrained and sent to Liselotte’s estate. For the record, Celia and Aishia were returned to their rooms by Rio’s judgment before Aria had arrived, leaving Rio alone to answer the questions but avoiding confrontation with Aria.

“...I see. Then I shall drop by tomorrow morning to apologize,” Liselotte said with a bitter face.

This is the worst possible occurrence. I didn’t want him to think of us as arrogant nobles... but an incident like this would definitely cause him to become more cautious.

There were many commoners that held the preconceived notion of nobles as arrogant. While that was due to the actual number of nobles that acted arrogantly towards common folk, Liselotte did not consider that a good thing. For a merchant like Liselotte, getting along with people began with trust — obviously, no one would form trade deals with someone they couldn’t trust.

“Understood. Then, I shall make the appropriate preparations,” Aria said respectfully.

“While I would like nothing more than to accompany you...” Duke Huguenot interrupted with terribly distraught words, trailing off.

“...It pains me to say this, but with your position as Sir Stewart’s father, it may be best if you didn’t appear before Sir Haruto, lest you make him more wary,” Liselotte said with difficulty. She feared that Rio would not wish to see the parent of an assailant, instead preferring to be apologized to directly by the perpetrator. Although that may not be the case.

“I figured.” Duke Huguenot frowned impatiently.

“Would you allow me to explain the situation on your behalf to Sir Haruto? After that, I shall prepare a proper opportunity for you to apologize,” Liselotte suggested for Duke Huguenot’s sake.

“Of course. Please tell him that I have nothing but good faith towards him and intend to settle my foolish son’s failures appropriately,” Duke Huguenot agreed immediately. It was extremely rare for someone in the position of a duke to apologize to a commoner, which was perhaps a sign of how highly valued the skills of the person named Haruto were.

“Understood.” Like Huguenot, Liselotte also valued Rio highly, and didn’t want their relationship to be ruined over such a trivial matter. That was why she needed to approach this with the utmost care and respect.

Tomorrow’s going to be a long day. Liselotte sighed quietly as to expel her exhaustion.

◇　◇　◇

After Duke Huguenot finished his discussion with Liselotte, he summoned Stewart and Alphonse to the guest bedroom he was staying in. As soon as he saw their faces, Duke Huguenot spat out scornful words filled with rage.

“You utter fools...”

“...” Stewart and Alphonse shook in absolute fear. They had completely sobered up already, their faces pale as ghosts.

“F-Father, I...” Stewart began to say something, but Duke Huguenot shut him up without hesitation.

“Silence. I barely had any expectations left for you, but this incident has left me in utter disappointment. I believe I told you before... that there would be no next time,” Duke Huguenot said to Stewart, his words filled with cold rage.

“B-But...”

“I said — silence.”

“...” Stewart had no other choice but to remain quiet.

“Ruining my relationship with a swordsman of that ability, smearing dirt over my name, and even causing Liselotte such great inconvenience. Rejoice, boy. Since you wish it so dearly, I will disinherit you,” Duke Huguenot shot with a sneer.

“D-Disinherit?! Duke Huguenot, that’s going too far!” Alphonse objected to Duke Huguenot in shock.

Disinheritance was a system that allowed the head of the family to revoke the right of inheritance to those who had the right to it. In terms of private punishments, it was the second most severe penalty after disownment. The moment disinheritance was announced publicly, Stewart would lose his position to become the next Duke Huguenot, so it was understandable that Alphonse would make a fuss.

“I do not recall allowing you to speak, either, Alphonse.” Duke Huguenot said coldly, looking at him.

“B-But this is too much over a simple quarrel with a mere commoner, a swordsman!” Alphonse flared up, making light of Rio.

“A mere commoner? Him? Did you not witness his sword skills with your own eyes?” Duke Huguenot said, looking down on Alphonse with contempt.

“...Sword skills aside, a commoner is a commoner!” Sensing he was being looked down upon, Alphonse argued back undauntedly.

“And what of it? Do you see yourself being far more skilled than him?” Duke Huguenot returned coolly.

“What did you say?!” For a moment, Alphonse forgot Duke Huguenot was ranked above him.

“You sure are an emotional person. I see... Perhaps you do suit the military more than politics. Though you’d be terribly incompetent either way,” Duke Huguenot stated flatly.

Alphonse reached his limit. “H-How dare you! I don’t care if you’re a duke — take back those words right this instant!”

“I do not feel the need to. You are incompetent.”

“Then — Then I’d like to hear the reason why you think I’m incompetent!” Alphonse said, breathing heavily through his nose.

“...Both Liselotte and I were discussing ways to scout him onto our side. Yet you, greatly misjudging his value, ruined that possibility. If that isn’t incompetence, what shall I call it? He’s capable of leading three minotaurs around by the nose. Could you do the same?” Heavily exasperated, Duke Huguenot asked his questions to provoke the younger man.

Three minotaurs. Since he had been there to witness them with his own eyes, Alphonse knew what a threat they had been. That’s why Alphonse calmed down for a moment... And yet, he couldn’t back down.

“...If I had an enchanted sword too, then yes.”

“Enchanted sword? Hahaha. So, you’re going for the sword next. Using an enchanted sword also requires an appropriate amount of talent. I do not see you possessing such talent for that.” Duke Huguenot said, not even bothering to humor him.

Having just made a bold statement, Alphonse couldn’t back down easily, either. “T-That’s not true!”

“Even though the two of you tried to attack him, two-on-one, and had the tables turned on you instead?” Duke Huguenot said with a huff of laughter.

“Guh...” Alphonse’s face crinkled in humiliation, but suddenly, the direction of the conversation began to change.

“But, well... Since you’re willing to go that far, I can give you a chance to clear your name. Otherwise, I wouldn’t be able to look your father in the face,” Duke Huguenot suddenly said.

“I-I’ll do it! Please allow me to do it!” Alphonse offered without listening to the details. That was another part of him Duke Huguenot found incompetent, but he didn’t point it out.

Duke Huguenot calmed Alphonse flatly before he got to the point. “All right — just listen first. Considering the number of monsters that attacked us, Liselotte wants to investigate the forest to the west of Amande...”

“So you want me to assist in that investigation?” Alphonse asked angrily.

“Well, aren’t you quick on the uptake. There may be survivors of the monsters lurking in the woods... If you do well as an advance party, I can put in a good word for you to your father. Of course, if you fail, you’ll be sent back to Rodania and placed on house arrest.”

“Please, let me do this!”

“Very well. However, the condition is that you apologize to Haruto with sincerity.”

“Wha...!” Alphonse, who had been ready and raring to go, balked at the condition Duke Huguenot attached.

“Is something the matter? Whether you are a competent person or not is a different issue to apologizing for causing trouble. Naturally, you must settle those debts. I plan on negotiating with Liselotte to obtain such an opportunity for you to do so. Oh, and make sure you apologize to her, too,” Duke Huguenot said, cornering Alphonse with his well-reasoned logic.

“I... I understand.” Alphonse clenched his teeth at the humiliation and nodded his head at the end. Before he knew it, he had no other options left.

“That is good to hear. Then, shall we practice? Apologize for causing me inconvenience with this incident. Put your heart into it. That goes for you too, Stewart,” Duke Huguenot demanded nonchalantly.

“Wha...?” The sudden demand caused Stewart and Alphonse to both freeze inadvertently.

“What’s the matter? I told you to apologize.” Duke Huguenot ordered coolly.

At that, his son shook with a flinch. “P-Please forgive me, father,” Stewart said reflexively.

“Guh... I’m sorry, Duke Huguenot.” With no other choice, Alphonse also apologized quietly.

“Worthless. You mean ‘please accept my apologies,’ no?” Duke Huguenot said to the two with heavy exasperation.

“Kuh...” Stewart and Alphonse both winced, but Duke Huguenot was completely serious. He didn’t intend on showing them any mercy.

“...Please, accept my apologies,” the two said with extreme discomfort, their voices nearly disappearing as they spoke.

“I believe I told you to apologize with sincerity. How about you at least lower your heads? Foreheads go against the ground. Can you not even do that?” Duke Huguenot spat with stern disappointment, not bothering to hide the exasperation in his voice.

“P-Please, accept my apologies...” Stewart prostrated himself on the ground in a fluster, heavily shaken up.

“Guh! S-Stewart!” Alphonse nearly burst in rage, but seeing Stewart fling aside his pride made him stop just before doing so.

“Is something the matter, Alphonse? If you refuse to do this, then you can forget what we just discussed. Otherwise, apologize now,” Duke Huguenot urged Alphonse coldly.

“...” Alphonse’s body was trembling with anger, but he dropped to his knees after a moment.

On this day, he experienced the greatest humiliation of his life.

◇　◇　◇

The next morning, Rio and the girls were having a peaceful breakfast together, completely at odds from the previous night.

“All things considered, last night was harrowing for a moment there. My heart’s still pounding. You’re sure it’s okay now, right? We won’t be involved in anything weird?” Celia checked with Rio worriedly.

“Yes. Aria has firmly sworn that nothing bad will come out of it for us. She wanted us to put our trust in Liselotte.” Rio smiled with a nod to reassure Celia.

“I see...” Still, Celia nodded worriedly.

“...I’m sorry, I’ve caused you a lot of worry by going along with me. How about you and Aishia stay in the stone house from today onward instead?” he suggested. Celia had already been taking extra care not to run into her old friend Aria, and now she had been dragged into an incident with her former students in an unforeseen way. It had been one problem after another since yesterday.

“No! I’m fine, really!” Celia shook her head in a fluster.

“But...” Rio frowned.

“I’m fine, I said. It’s not like issues like that will happen every day, right?” Celia said with a strained smile.

“But you won’t be able to rest properly this way.”

“That’s okay. I don’t want to be separated from you, anyway.” Celia’s will was firm — these were her true feelings.

“...” Unsure of what to say, Rio simply looked lost for words.

“Ah, t-that’s just because I’m worried, though!” Celia must have found her words embarrassing, as her words came out in a fluster.

Rio giggled and smiled happily. “Okay. Thank you.”

“Y-Yeah. A-Anyway, isn’t it dangerous outside of Amande right now? With that many monsters lurking and all...” Celia said rapidly, trying to hide her embarrassment. However, she had a point: Amande’s outskirts were certainly dangerous at the moment. That being said, the outskirts of Amande being off limits didn’t prevent them from staying further away from the city, and with Aishia there, anything that could happen would be dealt with easily.

“...Yes, you do have a point,” Rio said, respecting Celia’s decision. “Then, we’ll continue to stay at this inn. Thanks anyway, Aishia.”

Aishia had been shoveling food into her mouth silently, but when addressed by Rio, she agreed quietly. “No worries. If worse comes to worst, we can just run.”

Rio was dazed for a second, before he chuckled. “...Just run. Run, huh? Ahaha, well, I guess.”

“Hey, it’s no laughing matter. What will we do if it really comes to that?” Celia complained, but she was smiling softly.

“Leave it to me. Running away from the oppression of power is my specialty,” Rio said jokingly with a shrug.

“Geez,” Celia murmured, smiling in a show of exasperation.

◇　◇　◇

After the three of them finished breakfast and returned to their rooms, Liselotte’s carriage arrived with almost perfect timing.

Liselotte stepped down from the carriage and brought only Aria as her attendant towards Rio’s room. Then, she knocked on the door politely.

The door opened immediately and Rio stepped out. “Oh my, Lady Liselotte. Good morning to you.”

“Good morning, Sir Haruto — I apologize for intruding upon you so early in the morning. I am calling on you today to apologize for the incident last night and explain the particulars of how it was dealt with. May I have a moment of your time?” Liselotte bowed politely as soon as she saw Rio. Behind her, Aria also tipped her head.

“Yes, of course. I had heard from Aria in advance, but I didn’t expect you to pay a visit in person directly, Lady Liselotte. I would have gone to you if you had given the word.” Rio had assumed a messenger would come to summon him to her estate, after all.

“The one being apologized to shouldn’t have to answer to the whims of the one at fault,” Liselotte said with a troubled face.

“I appreciate your consideration. Please, do come in... If that is okay? Would you prefer somewhere else?” Rio seemed to feel Liselotte’s sincerity as he bowed his head in return and invited her inside the room. However, he hesitated as to whether or not it was appropriate to invite her into his room or change locations. Liselotte seemed to feel the same.

“Umm, anywhere you feel comfortable with is fine.”

“Then please, come inside,” Rio said, deciding to invite her in. “We may chat in the living room.”

It was a questionable choice to invite Aria into the same room as Celia, but since they were staying in such an extravagant inn for free, it was only proper to introduce them to the person who had paid them a direct visit. He planned to introduce Celia and Aishia to Liselotte and Aria quickly, then dismiss them afterwards. However —

“Understood. Then you shall remain here on standby,” Liselotte ordered Aria.

“Yes, my lady.” Aria nodded respectfully. Normally, it would be unthinkable for someone as highly ranked as Liselotte to step into the domain of a fairly unknown stranger without a guard.

“...Then, this way.” Despite being taken aback, Rio invited Liselotte into the room. He assumed it was another way for Liselotte to show her sincerity.

Celia and Aishia were waiting inside.

“Uh...” When Liselotte spotted them, her eyes widened in surprise. She often met with attractive people through her work connections, but these two were exceptionally beautiful. It was almost as though they had an aura that was impossible to put into words.

Chapter 6: Their Respective Nights

Just past evening that same day, in a guest room of Liselotte’s mansion in Amande. Duke Huguenot had finished his dinner and was listening to the captain of the elite guard, Raymond Brandt, give his report.

“...The investigation squad didn’t return?” Duke Huguenot asked with a furrowed brow.

“Yes, I believe something unforeseen must have happened,” Raymond reported with a pale face.

“Something unforeseen? Did we not discuss forming an advance squad with our knights with a focus on fighting ability and mobility in order to deal with that?” Duke Huguenot asked detachedly.

“It would mean that the dispatched squad encountered a difficulty not even they could deal with.”

“Do you mean to say a higher number of monsters were lurking than expected?”

“It is also possible that they simply had an accident...” Raymond said with difficulty. While the probability wasn’t zero, they were still knights that had undergone training. There was nothing more shameful than to have run into such trouble in the forest beside the city.

“...Very well. You may leave. I will send a directive shortly,” Duke Huguenot ordered, sighing deeply.

“Understood.” Raymond nodded with a stiff voice, then turned around. After a moment, the door swung shut.

“It seems we really are lacking soldiers with military capability. That squad should have included Alphonse, too... So he really was incompetent.”

Duke Huguenot’s irritated voice echoed through the empty room.

◇　◇　◇

Meanwhile, elsewhere in Liselotte’s mansion, Hiroaki was having after-dinner tea with Flora and Roanna in a guest living room separate to the guest bedrooms.

“...” The usually talkative Hiroaki was drinking tea silently for some reason. Flora also seemed a little dazed, but she was never very chatty to begin with.

It’s quiet... Roanna quietly watched Hiroaki’s face, observing his vastly different behavior.

“...Hah.” With his teacup in hand, Hiroaki let out a long-suffering sigh. He seemed to be clearly exhibiting the signs of worrying about something. However, Flora remained in her dazed state, unresponsive to how oddly Hiroaki was behaving.

Princess Flora also seems listless. I wonder what’s gotten into her and Sir Hiroaki...

Roanna was unable to stand the strange air in the room any longer. “Umm, Sir Hiroaki, is something the matter?” she asked nervously.

“Hm? What?” Hiroaki replied in a rather curt voice. Roanna mustered her courage to speak up.

“Umm, you don’t seem to be very happy. If there’s anything bothering you...”

At that, even Flora finally noticed their conversation, turning her ear towards them.

“Nah, it’s not that anything’s the matter...” Hiroaki said, shaking his head exaggeratedly. Contrary to his words, his attitude clearly showed something was wrong, so Roanna quietly waited for him to continue speaking.

“Don’t you think Flora is acting weirder than me?” Hiroaki suddenly said, turning to Flora.

“...Huh?” Taken aback, Flora’s body shook.

Hiroaki watched her silently. “...”

“Ah, umm, did I do something strange?” Flora cocked her head in confusion.

“Hmm. So you’re not aware of it. Ever since we were attacked by the monsters, you’ve been restless, like your heart isn’t really in it,” Hiroaki said with slight displeasure. Roanna made a face of realization as something sprung to mind.

“I-I don’t believe that’s true...” Flora shook her head with a frown.

“Well, if that’s what you insist, then fine. It just seemed like that was the case to me, but what you say is probably right,” Hiroaki said sharply. The way he phrased it was enough for Flora to feel the need to confirm.

“U-Umm, what did I look like to you?”

“Hmm. Well, as an example, you seem to be rather interested in that man. You were always watching his face, you know?” Hiroaki said, watching Flora’s reaction with a sidelong glance.

“Ah, umm, by that man, you mean... Umm. Do you mean Sir Haruto?” she said hesitantly.

“Yeah. So you’re aware that the man I’m talking about is Haruto,” Hiraki said in an ill-tempered tone.

“Huh? No... Umm, that’s...”

Flora had no idea why Hiroaki would say such a thing. Being that she was raised as a princess, she was hardly pressed by others as it concerned her speech or actions; when combined with her natural disposition, she had no idea how to deal with it.

“Princess Flora represents all of us, so she is probably troubled by how to properly express gratitude towards him for saving us from our predicament. There’s also the fact Duke Huguenot seems to be trying to scout him,” Roanna said immediately, supporting Flora.

“Hmm, I see. Is that true?” Hiroaki asked somewhat dubiously.

“Y-Yes,” Flora said, nodding awkwardly.

“Well, I suppose I can understand that much. But still, that Haruto... Don’t you think you’re all acting a little too excited about him?” Hiroaki said with skepticism.

“That’s because you are so powerful. When your own position is so far above, it makes those surrounding you appear lower. For us regular people, he seems plenty amazing.” Roanna explained, complimenting Hiroaki in the same breath. If it were Flora, she probably wouldn’t have been able to make something up on the spot as cleverly.

“Ah, I see... So that’s how it is. Well, in that case, I guess it can’t be helped.” Hiroaki’s pride was pleased to receive the praise, making him smirk.

For Roanna’s sake I’ll quietly accept that for today, he thought. However, he was still disappointed in Flora.

Honestly, I can always count on Roanna to have a lively conversation. Flora’s cute, but there’s nothing beyond that.

Hiroaki spent time with Flora and Roanna on a daily basis, so he already knew what their personalities were like. Flora could be summarized in one word: shy. To put it nicely, she was reserved... but if one chose to be harsh, you could say she was gloomy. She didn’t seem to be used to socializing with men, so she barely spoke when she was in the presence of the opposite gender. Even when she was with Hiroaki, who she knew fairly well by now, there were awkward silences at times.

At the very least, she wasn’t the type of girl to aggressively pursue men. The fact that she assertively tried to talk to Haruto, despite that, didn’t sit right. He couldn’t help but feel unsatisfied that she was acting proactive towards the wrong person. He was thinking selfishly.

Hiroaki didn’t seem to be aware of it himself, but contrary to his aspirations, he didn’t have the guts to go about forming human relations all that well by himself. That’s what made him both easy and difficult to handle at the same time.

He was a spoiled and troublesome man.

◇　◇　◇

Flora bid farewell to Hiroaki and Roanna once the conversation died down and returned to the guest bedroom she had been allocated. Liselotte’s attendants helped her prepare a bath and change of clothes, leaving her to flop onto the bed afterwards.

...Was I really that strange today?

She was bothered by what Hiroaki had pointed out earlier; he had said she was showing too much interest in Haruto, and seemed rather unhappy about it.

However, it was an undeniable fact that she was interested in Haruto.

Rio. Haruto. Their names are different. Their hair colors are different. He had acquaintances that he had been with for a long time. That’s why he should be a different person, and yet...

She couldn’t help but overlap the sight of Haruto fighting the minotaur from behind and of Rio, who had fought the minotaur during the academy’s outdoor drill in order to save Flora.

It was why she couldn’t help but stare at Haruto all day today. If the others around her found it strange, then it was possible that Haruto thought the same.

Ugh, I’m so hopeless...

Flora felt a strong sense of self-hatred. Her head was spinning, unable to keep up with her thoughts, but she continued to question herself.

What do I even want to do about it, anyway? If Sir Haruto really is Rio, what would I do?

She couldn’t possibly confirm it by asking him, but even if Haruto really was Rio, she doubted he would tell her the truth. After all, the Kingdom of Beltrum had once pushed a false accusation on Rio, then returned his favor with enmity instead. There was no taking back that sin.

Do I apologize? What we did was something unforgivable, though...

Did she really want him to forgive her? If so, it seemed far too convenient for her.

“Nn...” Once she reached that conclusion, she hated herself even more than she had earlier. Her face twisted with tears.

◇　◇　◇

A short while ago, in a drawing room of Liselotte’s mansion...

“...And that’s what happened. At present, the status of our knights is unknown, but it would be appropriate to assume that they have run into some kind of trouble,” Duke Huguenot explained. He’d requested an emergency audience with Liselotte to report how the dispatched knights had yet to return.

“...I am sorry. I should have sent out personnel from my side too,” Liselotte apologized with a shamed expression.

“No, I was the one who requested that the advance squad be formed from our knights. It’s hard to believe that a squad of twenty knights lacked the combat power for an initial investigation. If anything, one would normally consider it overkill.” Duke Huguenot shook his head with a bitter smile. Without an escort target to protect getting in the way, twenty knights was enough to take down a minotaur. He had sent them with that in mind. If that hadn’t been enough, then this could no longer be called anything but bad luck.

“Even so...” Liselotte started to say something mournfully. However, Duke Huguenot lifted a hand to stop her.

“It’s not confirmed that they were entirely wiped out, though I suppose it is hard to imagine that they’ve simply become lost wandering the forest. However, we should be considering what to do next. Do I have that right?” Duke Huguenot stated calmly.

“...Yes. However, in the event that the worst has happened, I will provide the maximum compensation,” Liselotte said in a resolute voice after taking in a deep breath.

“I apologize for being even more of a burden, but this is not an issue that should go unaddressed. We will do our best to resolve the situation. Let’s pull ourselves together.”

“...I appreciate that. As much as I want to send a follow-up squad right away, if an unforeseen situation has happened to as many as twenty knights, I must be careful in selecting personnel.”

It was no exaggeration to say that the title of a knight was proof that a human had obtained military ability of the highest degree. Certain powerful, leading figures who could use enchanted swords and run through the battlefield displaying their superhuman prowess by temporarily enhancing their physical abilities with magic or sorcery were merely exceptions.

Of course, knights had differences in individual strength and squads had differences in experience, but there was no overlooking a formation of twenty knights being caught off guard.

Thus, the squad to be sent next needed to be selected with more military power, either by increasing the overall quantity or raising the individual quality.

If it’s come to this, I’ll have to send Aria, Liselotte thought.

Aria was the strongest subordinate she had. She normally kept Aria beside her as a guard, but she’d have to mobilize her in this situation.

“If you do send one, make it after daybreak. At earliest, after the sun rises. There’s still the possibility they’ll suddenly make their way back in the morning. I would say noon would be latest to reach a conclusion, do you agree?” Duke Huguenot said with a contemplative look. While it was a little slow-paced, it would be reckless to enter the forest at night. If the search party ran into trouble, their efforts would be meaningless.

“Yes,” Liselotte nodded immediately, having thought exactly the same.

“However, I do believe most of the monsters were cleaned up in the earlier battle.”

“...There were some monsters that fled back into the forest, but I don’t really want to consider that possibility. You mean to imply that there might be minotaurs left behind — is that correct?” Duke Huguenot and Liselotte frowned together.

As an estimate, there were roughly several hundred monsters that attacked them earlier — a number no normal city would have in their vicinity even if they were all rounded up. On top of that, minotaurs weren’t commonly spotted monsters to begin with. For several of them to be lurking about made the situation far too irregular.

“Perhaps. If I were to assume the worst case scenario, there could be more monsters than what appeared earlier still lurking. Although it’s not something I want to believe,” Duke Huguenot said bitterly. If that assumption were true, it would mean over a thousand monsters were hidden in the area surrounding Amande.

Liselotte also nodded bitterly. “Agreed.” If that many monsters were completely overlooked in the vicinity of the city, then it’s even stranger. But such preconceptions are what led us to the current situation anyway. She scolded her own naivety.

“I intend to send Aria out for this. I will also select several proficient attendants and soldiers and lend them enchanted swords.” She normally only allowed Aria to carry an enchanted sword, but she was going all-out this time.

“Understood. I would like nothing more than to offer some of my knights, but...”

“No, there is no need to mobilize any more of your knights for us. The next party shall be formed by my forces,” Liselotte said in an orderly manner. With twenty knights missing in the current situation, she couldn’t allow him to move any more of his personnel.

Duke Huguenot nodded heavily and brought up Haruto, who would be most reliable after his great earlier performance. “I understand. Then may I suggest that you inquire if Haruto would be willing to lend his assistance?”

“...It would be one thing to rely on an adventurer of Amande, but Sir Haruto is merely a commoner. Not to mention there are also women in his company...” Liselotte shook her head respectfully.

“True, one would normally turn to adventurers for cases like this.”

“Yes. But I will not be using adventurers this time. With such a high possibility of minotaurs still around, it’s possible the monsters might follow some kind of leadership like they did during the road attack. Preparations should be made in case Amande is attacked while short-handed.”

The biology of monsters wasn’t well understood, but it was known that they swarmed around powerful individuals and moved under their leadership towards a target. The monsters that had attacked them on the road were clearly following some kind of leadership, so it was most likely that a minotaur or humanoid monster had been leading the horde.

And if there really were minotaurs remaining, it was highly likely they would make planned movements, at worst placing the city in danger of attack. There were rarely any adventurers with skill on par with knights, but they were many in number. If the monsters attacked in droves, they would be a reliable source of combat power.

“That is a most justified decision,” Duke Huguenot said, nodding worriedly.

◇　◇　◇

Meanwhile, in the depths of the forest west of Amande, Lucius and Reiss were seated around a campfire. Surrounding them were countless dark-skinned revenants, standing silently. It made an extremely eerie sight.

“The bodies recreated towards the end should be completely settled soon.” Reiss chuckled in satisfaction as he looked around at the revenants.

“Good to hear... But the way they swarm around pisses me off. Put them away already,” Lucius demanded uneasily.

“Oh? I would have liked to keep my new collection up for a little longer to gaze upon them.”

“Hah, you really are a creepier bastard than I am.”

Reiss grinned. “Why, that’s because they’re basically my children. But if you insist, then I suppose I have no choice,” he said, breathing a small sigh. The revenants standing around them immediately began to sink into the earth.

“I can finally breathe again. Now I can have a good night’s rest, at least,” Lucius huffed through his nose in satisfaction.

“The plan will be set in motion tomorrow morning, before the sun rises. Make sure you don’t sleep in.”

“Hey, hey. Who do you think you’re talking to?”

“I suppose you would never sleep in before a fight, hmm?” Reiss said with a chuckle.

“If you’re going to worry about sleeping in, worry about our Alphonse, our newest member, over there. Right? Hey,” Lucius bantered lightly, looking over at the third person sitting by the fire to warm up. There sat a revenant with jet black skin far darker than the dark grey skin of the other revenants, silently watching on.

“...Hmph. In that case. You. Should have let me. Go to Amande alone. And clean up. Everything. Before the other defectives. Settle in.” The jet black revenant named Alphonse huffed unhappily through his nose before boasting in a terribly ghastly voice.

“Hahaha, what a revolting voice,” Lucius said lightly, mouth turned in a carefree grin.

“This is the final form of the revenant. While it is notably more powerful and aggressive than the enhanced version, it’s all intellect and no reason, making it difficult to handle,” Reiss muttered tiredly.

“But he’ll be of use in tomorrow’s attack, no?” Lucius asked, his mouth in a relaxed grin.

Reiss nodded in exasperation. “Well, yes.”

As a disposable pawn, anyway. His mouth twisted faintly in a repulsive smile.

“Well, that’s what it’s gonna be. We have high expectations of you, Alphonse,” Lucius said brightly, his smile completely hollow.

The jet black revenant nodded, his reply disjointed. “Yeah. I’ll kill them. All. Of them.” Nothing but hatred swirled within those eyes that had lost all sense of reason.

“Haha. How hopeless.”

Lucius’ disgusted laugh echoed throughout the quiet forest.

Interlude: Meanwhile, in the Proxia Empire

The Proxia Empire was a military superpower located north of the Strahl region. It boasted a large land size and bordered the Beltrum Kingdom to the south, which was shaped longer horizontally, whereas the Galarc Kingdom to the southeast was shaped longer vertically.

However, while its landsize was comparable to its vast military prowess, the Proxia Empire was, in actuality, an extremely young country established merely 40 years ago.

The founding emperor, Nidoll, was a former orphan born to a small and impoverished kingdom. Once he grew up and started working as a mercenary, he made a name for himself with his unparalleled fighting ability. After seizing sovereignty of the small kingdom he belonged to, he formed the Proxia Empire.

The lands to the north of the Strahl region had once been known as warring countries, high in number and small in size. Led by Nidoll, the Proxia Empire army stormed them one after another and expanded its land size in the blink of an eye. At the center of their military force were the elite demi-dragon knights, a squad formed of low ranked demi-dragons including winged lizards and lizard runners. They made use of the demi-dragons’ mobility to specialize in blitzkrieg-like attacks and capture over twenty small countries to date.

However, the strongest warrior that supported the Proxia Empire was not in the demi-dragon knights. The strongest person in the empire, both past and present, was the founding emperor — Nidoll Proxia.

Even in his sixties, Nidoll’s physical body showed no sign of old age; his enormous frame was still as hard as a boulder and fighting prowess as tremendous as ever, leaving both his own country and other countries in fear. Word of Nidoll’s military exploits had traveled wide and far throughout Strahl, making him undoubtedly the strongest in the entire region.

At present, somewhere in the imperial capital of the Proxia Empire, Nidgard, Nidoll stood on the wide balcony of the towering imperial castle, idly looking down at the cityscape of the capital below. While the area would normally be forbidden to even the nobles of the imperial court, from behind Nidoll spoke a friendly male voice.

“Yo, Nidoll. How’s it going?”

“Bored,” Nidoll replied listlessly. He didn’t bother to turn around, showing no interest in the man talking to him.

The young man was wearing the outfit of a soldier. His body was clad in high-quality combat clothes, and there was a sword hanging from his waist, but he showed none of the proper mannerisms of a knight.

“Ha. You’re always looking so damn depressed. Are you that restless for war? Actually, I’ve just been preparing an interesting stage for you to take part in,” the man said with a sneer.

“Hmph. My tastes don’t match yours. I’m not interested,” Nidoll answered with a huff.

The man shrugged his shoulders with a sigh. “Yeah, yeah. Stubborn as usual, I see. That aside, what are you gonna do? What about Beltrum? Though I’m not involved over there.”

“I couldn’t care less about that kingdom,” Nidoll stated bluntly.

“Now now, you shouldn’t be like that. It wouldn’t be fun if the Arbor faction fell now.”

“Don’t worry about that. As a sign of friendship and reassurance, I’ve sent an official goodwill ambassador. Nothing will come of their internal conflicts.”

“Hah. You sure went out of your way for a kingdom that’ll fall sooner or later.” Contrary to his words, the man gave a pleasant smile.

“I suppose we do agree there,” Nidoll said, huffing with a grin.

“Right. I guess I’ll be making my way back to the kingdom of Paladia now.” With nothing more to say, the man made to turn on his heel and leave, when another man’s voice rang through the terrace.

“Please wait a moment.”

“Ah? Well, if it ain’t Reiss,” the man turned back and said. There, standing before him, was the man in question.

“I’ve been searching for you, Mr. Lucius,” Reiss said, grinning with an emotionless smile.

“Hah, and you always seem to show up at the most convenient time for yourself,” Lucius said with a sneer.

Interlude: A Day in the Life of Miharu

Meanwhile, in the spirit folk village, Miharu was working hard at spirit art drills with Aki, under the guidance of Orphia.

“Hmph...” Aki groaned as she held her hand out in the empty space before her. Miharu also had her hand out before her, a water bubble several centimeters in diameter floating on her palm.

“That’s amazing, Miharu. Both your spirit art activation time and the size of the bubble has visibly developed in these last few days!” Orphia said, her eyes widening when she saw Miharu’s improvement.

“Thank you. I think I’m starting to get the hang of it. It’s all thanks to you, Orphia,” Miharu replied bashfully. She concentrated once again, turning her focus back to the use of spirit arts.

Aki stared at Miharu closely. “...I wonder what the difference is between Miharu and me. Is it really talent after all?” she murmured, frowning in disappointment. The more days went by, the greater the gap between her and Miharu grew, which probably made her feel impatient. While Aki’s murmurs didn’t reach Miharu in her concentration, they definitely reached Orphia’s ears.

Miharu’s talent is wonderful, of course, but... Orphia looked at Aki’s face before staring at Miharu’s serious side profile. While Orphia had no experience teaching spirit arts to a human outside of her experience with Rio, it was obvious that Miharu’s talent in spirit arts was clearly at an abnormal level.

That being said, Rio was a particularly unique exception for a human, and there was still the question of whether to group Miharu and the others as humans of this world when they had come from Earth. The only thing that was certain was that not only Miharu, but Aki and Masato too, were acquiring spirit arts at an incredible speed compared to the humans of this world. It was why Orphia repeatedly reminded Aki that there was no need for her to feel dejected. Unfortunately, it seemed there was no way to stop Miharu’s overwhelmingly rapid progress from making her feel inferior. Aki found herself feeling hopeless on occasion.

I wonder what the difference is between Miharu and Aki? Is it really just talent in the end? I don’t want to brush it off with that one excuse. The one who’s been working the hardest with her more mature age has been Miharu, after all. She’s concentrating really hard right now, too...

Miharu’s expression was the portrait of determination. Orphia also knew that Miharu had been tirelessly working away outside of their practice hours, too.

In contrast, possibly due to her attention being taken away by Miharu’s growth, Aki’s mind seemed rather restless at times. She didn’t seem to be having any distractions in her daily life, and while one option was to keep observing quietly for a little longer, Orphia found herself racking her brains as to why she couldn’t lead Aki better as both her elder and spirit arts instructor.

It might be best to talk to Miharu about it after all. I have things I want to discuss with her anyway, and she should know Aki best. Orphia may have been her instructor in spirit arts training, but Miharu was actually one year older than Orphia, so she felt like she could rely on her at a time like this.

Okay. I’ll do it tonight right away! And I’ll have to call Sara and Alma over too!

With that decided, Orphia giggled to herself.

◇　◇　◇

That night, in the village house where they all lived together...

After the younger group of Latifa, Aki, and Masato had gone to sleep, Orphia brought Sara and Alma along to Miharu’s bedroom and knocked quietly on the door.

“...Yes? What’s wrong, everyone?” Miharu was still awake, so she opened the door immediately. When she saw the older group of girls gathered outside, her eyes widened slightly.

“Fufufu, could the four of us have a little talk?” Orphia suggested to Miharu with a smile.

It was basically an invitation for an other-world version of a pajama party, and Miharu and the spirit folk girls were already in their sleepwear. While the residents of the house would regularly gather in the living room to drink tea at night, it was rare for only the older girls to gather together, much less visit Miharu’s bedroom.

“Sure, come in.” Miharu readily welcomed the three girls inside.

“Thank you.” Orphia and the others entered the bedroom happily. Miharu’s room was roughly 15 square meters large, with a small table in the corner of the room. Orphia placed the tray on that table.

“Were you practicing spirit arts just now?” Sara asked, looking around the room.

Miharu nodded hesitantly. “Ah... yeah. How did you know?”

“There are remnants of ode and mana waves flowing through your room. The ode density was greater than what the light artifacts give off, so I guessed you were practicing in secret,” Sara deduced with a giggle.

“I see...” Miharu mumbled quietly at Sara’s observational skills. The spirit art she had been using was an extremely minor one, but constantly repeating it had caused a significant amount of magic essence to be released without her realization.

“It seems like you were practicing a fair bit. You’re such a hard worker, Miharu.” Alma giggled.

“T-That’s not true.” Miharu shook her head in discomfort. It wasn’t as though practicing in private had been forbidden, but overworking would cause exhaustion and wasn’t recommended. She had been practicing spirit arts for nearly an hour before the girls had arrived, but she didn’t want to worry them.

However, Miharu couldn’t fool the eyes of Sara and the others, who were known as the leading talents in spirit arts in all the village.

“I can tell even if you try to hide it. It’s good that you’re hard-working, but when you’re a beginner, you have to be careful not to practice too much,” Sara warned Miharu with an exasperated tone.

“That’s right. I’ve told you many times already, but if you release too much ode from your body while you’re still inexperienced, you could ruin your health, you know?” Orphia noted, emphasizing Sara’s words with her own.

“I agree,” Alma nodded along.

“Ahaha, I don’t feel particularly bad or anything, so I’m sure it’s fine. I won’t practice anymore today. Now, have a seat.” Miharu laughed a little awkwardly, urging Sara and the others to sit.

“Okay. Excuse me.” Sara gave a helplessly strained smile before sitting down on a chair. Alma and Orphia followed her, and Orphia immediately began pouring tea.

“We normally gather in the living room, so meeting up in someone’s bedroom is a new feeling,” Alma said as she looked around the room.

“I agree. If we’re the only ones gathered, does that mean you have something important to talk about?” Miharu asked somewhat curiously, nodding while she gazed at their expressions.

“How about it, Orphia?” Sara must have been summoned by Orphia without knowing what the matter at hand was, as she tilted her head in question.

“Fufu, I suppose you could call it important. I wanted us to have a talk about Miharu, Aki, and Masato once more, just between the four of us,” Orphia said with a bright smile.

“Well, it’s true that we haven’t had the opportunity to discuss this...” Sara looked back on their living together until now with a thoughtful face. While she accepted Orphia’s reason more or less, she suspected that there was another motive behind it.

“Right.” Orphia clapped her hands together in front of her chest. “And so, Miharu... How has life been in the village? Do you have any worries, any woes? Anything that makes you anxious?”

“Huh? Umm... Not really, I guess?” Miharu was taken aback by the sudden interrogation, cocking her head as she replied.

“Really?” Orphia asked once more, peering at Miharu’s face.

“...Yeah. That’s the truth,” Miharu confirmed hesitantly.

“Do you suspect otherwise, Orphia?” Sara asked, cutting straight to the point.

“Hmm. It’s just the fact that they’re living in an unfamiliar village. I was wondering if they had any anxieties or problems outside of our knowledge. Not only for Miharu, but Aki and Masato too,” Orphia explained.

“I see. How about it, Miharu?” Sara asked.

“I haven’t had a problem with life at the village. We’re treated so well — I can’t be grateful enough to Haruto and everyone here,” Miharu answered with a cheerful laugh.

Sara resolutely asked what she had feared bringing up. “But aren’t you lonely? You’ve been separated from your family, too.” In order to prevent that, Sara and the others had put their utmost effort into welcoming them warmly, but there was a limit.

“I’d be lying if I said I wasn’t lonely, I think. As far as Aki, who at times doesn’t seem as energetic... She’s been separated from her beloved brother, so I think she ponders a lot about that,” Miharu uttered, showing a glimpse of a fleeting smile. “But I’m so grateful... my feelings of regret have all but dissipated. I truly believe we’re blessed to be in this situation right now. I’m so happy to have met everyone, you know?” She continued, laughing shyly.

“Miharu...” Orphia, Sara, and Alma all smiled quite happily.

“Of course, I believe Aki and Masato also feel the same way. That’s why, even if we might be lonely, we’ll be fine with everyone here. Thank you for always being with us.”

“We’re also grateful to have you guys here. I’m so happy we became friends,” Sara said with embarrassment.

“...Yeah.” Miharu nodded in a similar fashion.

“We’ll also try to keep an eye out for Aki and Masato, but please don’t hesitate to speak up if you need anything, Miharu,” Alma said.

“Thank you, Alma,” Miharu said happily. Orphia suddenly spoke up. “...How has your spirit arts training been going? I think Aki and Masato have been feeling a little impatient, as they’re unable to catch up to you.”

“Really? It didn’t seem like that to me...” Sara said in surprise.

“I could be overthinking things, but it seemed a little like that during training. I was wondering what she was like outside of training.” Orphia said, indirectly turning the question to Miharu.

“...I haven’t seen her bothered outside of training hours, as far as I know. I’ll also pay a little more attention from now on,” Miharu answered with a contemplative look. “Thank you, Orphia, for watching Aki closely.”

“It’s nothing. When it comes to spirit arts, I’m meant to be your teacher, after all. Though I may still be lacking at times,” Orphia said with a strained smile.

Miharu shook her head. “That’s not true. The way you teach is so good — I can definitely tell I’m improving bit by bit,” she said, advocating for Orphia as the secret to her rapid growth.

“That’s because you’re so talented. Not only that — the fact you’re the hardest working when it comes to spirit arts training also plays a large part.” No matter how much talent she had, it would’ve been wasted if she hadn’t been motivated.

“And it seems like you’ve been practicing secretly too,” Sara said with a laugh.

“I-It wasn’t that much.” Miharu defended herself in embarrassment.

“You seem really ambitious about it, but is there a reason why?” Alma giggled, wondering why Miharu worked so hard at it.

“Part of it is because it’s fun, but...” Miharu trailed off halfway, causing Sara and the others to all urge her to continue in unison.

“But?”

“But even while we’re living peacefully, Haruto must be working hard out there, right? I feel bad leaving everything for him to deal with like this...” Miharu replied bashfully, feeling everyone’s attention gathered on her.

“I see, so it’s for Rio’s sake.” Alma seemingly emphasized Rio’s name in understanding.

“Ufufu, I see. So that’s how it is,” Orphia said happily. Meanwhile, Sara was glancing at Miharu’s expression silently.

“...Umm, is everyone misunderstanding something?” Realizing she was on the receiving end of the three meaningful gazes made Miharu blush.

“Misunderstanding what?” Alma asked back innocently.

“No, umm... I just don’t want to be a hindrance to Haruto like this. He saved us, so I want to increase the number of things I can do as much as possible... So the next time something happens, I can’t be left behind...” Miharu defended herself in a fluster, blushing all the more.

“Yes, it goes without saying that everyone understands your reason for working so seriously now.” Alma said, a gentle smile tugging at her lips.

“So you want to be with Rio.” Orphia said, nodding along.

“T-That’s not it! I-I mean, you’re not wrong, but!” Miharu objected in vexation. She was extremely frustrated at how she was unable to do anything in return for the person who had done so much for her, a stranger. She refused to be content at remaining a hindrance to him.

That was why Miharu worked so hard. If she at least became strong enough to protect herself, she could stay by Rio’s side. If she didn’t work hard while she could, it somehow felt like Rio would one day go somewhere far away. She didn’t want that to happen.

She didn’t want Rio to leave her behind. It was hard to describe using words, but she was utterly terrified of that happening.

“Well, if that’s why your spirit arts learning is going so fast, then it’s fine, right? Being able to reach activation in such a short time is an impressive feat, no?” Sara giggled, supporting Miharu with all she had.

“Right. It’s a result obtained by combining Miharu’s talent and hard work,” Orphia agreed with a grin.

“But even for that, I feel it’s a little too fast... Honestly, the speed is on par with the higher ranks of the village. Although there are barely any people who start learning at Miharu’s age, so it simply may be a case of having nothing to compare with...” Alma said with a contemplative look.

“While I’d certainly understand if she had been contracted to some kind of spirit, that isn’t the case for Miharu. Although, she is a citizen of another world, I suppose,” Sara pondered out loud.

“Contracted to a spirit? Huh?” Miharu uttered, blinking as though she had realized something.

“Is something the matter, Miharu?” Orphia cocked her head and asked.

“This was before we came to the village, but I remember when Rio came here without us to explain the circumstances, Ai-chan formed a temporary pact with me in order to replenish her magic essence,” Miharu explained, the memory suddenly resurfacing from the back of her mind.

“...That’s it,” Orphia said with wide eyes. Sara and Alma also blinked in surprise.

“It’s the reason why I can learn spirit arts so fast, right?”

“Yes. The connection used in a temporary pact cannot match that of a real contract, but Lady Aishia is a humanoid spirit. She must have awakened your talent in spirit arts,” Sara explained.

“So that’s how it was... I’ll have to thank Ai-chan when she gets back.” Miharu looked back on her memories with Aishia and found herself smiling with a giggle.

Epilogue

Just what time was it? And where was this place?

Miharu wondered vaguely in her drowsy consciousness.

“Miharu.” Someone called her name.

Ai-chan... Yes, it was Aishia’s voice.

Before she knew it, Aishia was standing before Miharu. Aishia stared at Miharu’s face closely. “Though it’s temporary, a connection between your soul and mine will be made because of the path formed. Is that all right?” she asked suddenly.

“Umm, is there a problem with having connected souls?” Miharu’s mouth moved regardless of her own will to confirm nervously.

Ah, this is a dream. From before we came to the village... Miharu became aware that she was within her own dream, vividly reliving a past event.

“Not particularly. Maybe the occasional empath moments?” Aishia answered with a tilt of her head.

“Empath?”

“Our minds may connect with each other.”

“Umm, what will happen when it does?” Miharu couldn’t quite picture it in her head and sought a more specific explanation.

“The other person’s mind and memories might be transmitted to you in some form. Like déjà vu. I’m able to intentionally create an empath effect if we’re in direct contact, but I can’t trigger it willingly from afar. It won’t happen often, either. And it’s uncontrollable. But it might happen when either one of us is feeling a strong emotion,” Aishia explained carefully for Miharu’s sake. While one would normally feel creeped out and dislike it, Miharu showed no reluctance at all, accepting the temporary path with Aishia.

“That’s fine. Use my magic essence until Haruto returns.”

“...Okay, thank you,” Aishia said.

Thus, this was how Miharu and Aishia formed their temporary path. But why was she having a dream about it now? Miharu pondered with her drowsy mind, but she didn’t know. As she was thinking, her vision changed once more. A different dream seemed to be beginning.

Who is that? Miharu blinked in wonder. A black-haired mother and her similarly black-haired child of around five years old were happily walking in front of her with their hands linked. They seemed to be located in a city somewhere in Strahl.

“Hey, Mom. Why do you and I have black hair? We’re the only ones different to the people around us.” The boy asked his mother curiously.

“Well, you see, Rio. That’s because your father and I came here from far away, I think.” The mother answered the boy’s question with a troubled face.

Rio? That’s... Haruto? And Haruto’s mother? She’s beautiful... Once Miharu realized she was looking at a young Rio, she watched his mother in a daze.

“Do all the people who live far away have black hair?” Rio asked curiously.

“Yes, that’s right. It’s not just you and me. Your father’s hair was black, your grandpa’s hair was black, and your grandma’s was as well,” his mother answered with a gentle smile.

“Huh... I want to meet grandma and grandpa someday.” Rio watched his mother’s smile and grinned in return.

“...Let’s see. I’ll take you to meet them once you’ve grown up. They’re in a place called the Yagumo region,” his mother said with yet another troubled smile.

“Really? It’s a promise?”

Rio’s smile was too innocent to turn down. “Yup, it’s a promise.” The woman gave a motherly smile and nodded with a voice filled with affection. It was a warm, beautiful day in the life of a parent and child.

However, Miharu’s vision changed once again. There, the mother who had been holding Rio’s hand and walking mere moments ago, was being pinned down face-up by a well-built man.

“Hey Rio, are you frustrated?” The man sneered with a chilling grin, his weapon pierced through the mother’s body. Young Rio cowered and cried as he reached for his mother in a daze.

Uh... Miharu couldn’t help but avert her gaze from the scene.

Suddenly, a grown-up Rio stood right beside her. His hair was grey and he was wearing the outfit Miharu was used to seeing him in. Rio had his sword grasped tightly in his hand as he stared fixedly at the gruesome scene.

Ah, H-Haruto... He shouldn’t look, Miharu thought, but her mouth wouldn’t open.

Rio paid no attention to Miharu’s presence, merely watching the tragedy with a terribly cold gaze. After a moment, Rio started walking towards the man.

Miharu couldn’t tear her eyes away. She knew immediately what Rio was trying to do. In the next moment, Rio cut the man’s head off without a moment of hesitation.

Ah! That was where Miharu’s mind went drowsy again. Her consciousness was rapidly fading. When she opened her eyes in the morning, she might lose her memories of the dream.

N-No, I can’t. Don’t wake up... Miharu didn’t want to know such a sad story, but she didn’t want to forget, either. Her memory of this dream was something she thought shouldn’t be forgotten. She thought it was something she should look at straight-on, no matter how painful it was. Scared, sad, frustrated, and helpless, Miharu couldn’t do anything but embrace the Rio in her dreams.

Her heart hurt... But that was when the door to her memories slammed shut heavily. Miharu’s mind finally faded away...

And dawn broke.